Clark W. Thompson papers, Inclusive: 1931-1966, undated, Bulk: 1959-1966
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Clark W. Thompson papers
Inclusive: 1931-1966, undated, Bulk: 1959-1966
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
100
Thompson, Clark Wallace, 1896 - 1981
96 document boxes and 8 oversize boxes
The Clark Thompson papers focus on Representative Thompson's years as a member of the United States House of Representatives. Materials include correspondence, legislation, invitations to events, communications with the media, and scrapbooks containing memorabilia of Thompson’s tenure in Congress.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Clark Wallace Thompson III was born on August 6, 1896 in La Crosse, Wisconsin to Clark Wallace Thompson and Jessie Marilla (Hyde) Thompson. Five years later, his family moved to Oregon where Thompson spent the remainder of his childhood and adolescence. He attended the University of Oregon at Eugene where he was a member of Phi Delta Theta, an international social fraternity. In 1917, Thompson enlisted in the United States Marine Corps (USMC) and served for the duration of America's involvement in World War I. Following the war, he remained a member of the Marine Corps Reserves and in 1936 organized the Fifteenth Battalion of the USMC Reserves. His decades-long involvement in the military and his passion for national defense heavily influenced his political career.
In 1918, Clark Thompson married Libbie Moody, the daughter of William L. Moody, Jr. and Libbie Rice Shearn of Galveston, Texas. The Moody family had been long-established in Galveston society and business where the newlyweds soon settled. The Thompsons had two children, Clark and Libbie.
Thompson served as the treasurer of the American National Insurance Company and left to start his own mercantile firm which he owned until 1932. He was also secretary-treasurer of the Cedar Lawn Development Company until 1934. In 1933, Clark Thompson was elected to the House of Representatives from the 7th district of Texas to fill the vacancy left by the death of Representative Clay Stone Briggs. He served as a Democrat until 1935.
With the outbreak of World War II, Thompson was once again called upon to serve his country and was ultimately sent to the southwestern Pacific theater where he was the oldest officer in his unit. In 1943, he returned to the United States and became the Director of the Marine Corps Reserves. He held this position for three years until his retirement as a colonel in 1946. For his service, Thompson was awarded the Legion of Merit.
From 1947 to 1966, Thompson returned to politics and represented the 9th district of Texas after significant redistricting. Throughout his political career, Thompson served on several different committees including Agriculture, Maritime and Fisheries, and Ways and Means. While living in Washington, D.C., Clark and Libbie Thompson were important members of the social scene in the 1950's and 1960's. Their house was often referred to as the “Texas Embassy” or the “Texas Legation.”
Thompson was a lifelong member of the Episcopal Church as well as a member of the American Legion. He was also involved in the Veterans of Foreign Wars, the Texas State Society, and was a thirty-second-degree Mason and Shriner. Clark Thompson passed away on December 16, 1981, in Galveston, Texas, and was buried in Galveston Memorial Park Cemetery.
Scope and Content
The Clark Thompson papers focus on Representative Thompson's years of service in the United States House of Representatives. The papers range from 1931 to 1966, but the bulk of the collection dates from 1959-1966, the last few years of Thompson's time in Washington.
The Administrative and Agencies series consists of materials related to government agencies in the 1960's, including Thompson’s final years in the House of Representatives. This series contains information on various government agencies, such as the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, the Federal Aviation Administration, and the Small Business Administration.
Thompson served on several committees over the course of his legislative career. Series II. Committees reflects the committees on which he served, primarily the Agricultural, Maritime and Fisheries, and Ways and Means Committees.
Series III. Correspondence mostly contains the replies Thompson sent to various inquiries. In most cases, the original letter is not attached. The correspondence deals with various political and personal topics.
Materials in Series IV. Departments primarily consist of executive department information from the Agriculture, Post Office, and Health, Education, and Welfare Departments.
Series V., Legislative, contains bills and legislation from Thompson’s congressional terms. The materials are sorted according to the Congress (in two-year increments). One significant collection of folders pertains to the Panama Canal, an issue Thompson focused on specifically. The series has materials that span from the 1940's to the 1960's.
Series VI. Personal, as the name suggests, consists of various personal papers, including invitations sent to Thompson regarding events in both Washington, D.C. and the state of Texas. Clark and Libbie Thompson were popular figures in Washington's social scene in the 1950's and 1960's. The series also houses campaign materials from Thompson's first foray into politics as well as records from his last years in office.
Series VII. Public contains Thompson's communications with congressional districts, other branches of the government, and members of the media. This series illustrates how Thompson’s methods of communicating with his constituents evolved dramatically over time.
Series VIII. Scrapbooks contains eight scrapbooks spanning the years 1946-1964. These are filled with photographs, clippings, and other memorabilia from Thompson’s tenure in Congress.
Thompson's adopted state, Texas, is featured in the final series of his collection, Texas Affairs. This series includes a wide range of materials about his state and local area. As Galveston is a major coastal city, most of the documents in this series relate to the use and construction of local harbors, weather disasters, and public water access. Several folders pertaining to the Texas City Disaster contain correspondence, litigation, and legislation dealing with the aftermath of an industrial accident that occurred in 1947.
Arrangement
The Clark Thompson papers were previously processed and originally organized into five series arranged alphabetically. Three original subseries (Administrations/Agencies, Committees, and Departments) were removed from the Legislative series and each became a new, separate series. The Correspondence series was rearranged topically for ease of access.
The current arrangement has nine series, and all are arranged alphabetically. The nine series are: Administrations/Agencies, Committees, Correspondence, Departments, Legislative, Personal, Public, Scrapbooks, and Texas Affairs.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 100. Acquired 2016-00-00
Related Resources
Related references
Butler III, Patrick H.," Thompson, Clark Wallace." "Handbook of Texas Online." 2010 June 15.
Find A Grave, Inc. "Clark Wallace Thompson." Memorial no. 7775083. Databases. Accessed 2019 December 05. [newspaper]
"Thompson, Clark Wallace." Biographical Directory of the United States Congress.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
United States. Congress. House. Committee on Agriculture--Officials and employees.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Merchant Marine and Fisheries.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Ways and Means; United States. Congress. House.
Places
Galveston (Tex.) -- History.; Panama Canal (Panama); Texas -- History -- 20th century.; Texas--Politics and government--20th century.
Subjects
Administrative agenciesDLUnited States.; Legislation--Texas.; Legislation--United States.; Legislators -- Texas.; Political campaigns -- Texas.
Genres
Albums (Books); Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Invitations.; Legislative bills.; Legislative materials.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Radio scripts.; Records (Documents); Speeches.; Television scripts.
- Administrations/Agencies, 1959-1966, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Administrations and Agencies series contains materials that pertain to subsets of the executive and legislative branches from the 1960's. This series focuses on documents related to government administrations like the Federal Aviation Administration, the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, and the Small Business Administration. The folders are arranged mainly in alphabetical order, and overall, the series is in good condition.
  - American Medical Association, General, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Medical Association, Advisory Committee, 1966 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee on Intergovernmental Relations, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, General, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, General, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Waste Disposal, General, 1959 March-June (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Waste Disposal, General, 1959 July-September (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Waste Disposal, General, 1959 October-December (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Waste Disposal, General, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Waste Disposal, Clippings, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Waste Disposal, Bill and Press Releases, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Atomic Energy Act, Opinion and Final Decision, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Nuclear Development Plans in Texas, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Civil Defense, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Civil Service Commission, General, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service Commission, Cases, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Civil Service Commission, Cases, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Civil Works, Fiscal Year 1962 Amended Budget (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Farmers Home Administration, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, General, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, General, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, General, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, Federal Aid Airport Program, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, Federal Aid Airport Program, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, Federal Aid Airport Program, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, Moody Memorial Church Steeple, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, Scholes Field Site, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Federal City Council, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1963 January-March (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1963 March-August (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1963 August-1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Federal Communications Commission (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Federal Communications Commission (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Federal Housing Administration, Cases, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Federal Power Commission (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Federal Power Commission (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1959-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - General Accounting Office, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - General Services Administration, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General Services Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Housing and Finance, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Labor, National Relations Board, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Library of Congress, Book Surplus, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, General, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Maritime Administration, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1962 January-May (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1962 June-December (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1963 January-September (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1963 October-1964 November (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, General, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, International Cooperation in Space, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Invitation to Edward C. Welsh, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Photos from H. T. Cristman, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Photos from O. G. Lindquist, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Texas Highway Commission, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, General, 1965 December-1966 January (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, General, 1966 February-May (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, General, 1966 July-November (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, Bay Ridge Christian College, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Patent Office, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Poverty Program, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Poverty Program, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1961-1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Small Business Administration, General, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Administration, General, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Small Business Administration, General, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Small Business Administration, General, 1964 January-July (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Small Business Administration, General, 1964 August-December (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Small Business Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Small Business Administration, Ballot for Congressmen from National Foundation of Infectious Diseases, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Small Business Administration, Planning and Coordinating Administration Management Courses, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Small Business Administration, Simplified Bank Loan Participation Plan, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Tariff Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Tariff Commission, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Committees, 1961-1966; 2
  Series II. Committees contains materials related to legislative committees in the House of Representatives. Unsurprisingly, a significant portion of these committee materials pertain to Thompson’s service on the Agriculture, Maritime and Fisheries, and Ways and Means Committees, but information regarding other congressional committees is also present. The series is mainly in alphabetical order and is in good condition.
  - Agriculture, General, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, General, 1963 January-May (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, General, 1963 June-December (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, General, 1964 January-July (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, General, 1964 July-December (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, General, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, Cases, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, Cotton, 1962 November-1963 May (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, Cotton, 1963 June-September (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture, Cotton, 1963 October-December (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture, Cotton, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Agriculture, Cotton, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture, Cotton, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Agriculture, Farmer’s Bulletin, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, H.R. 4997, Feed Grain Bill, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, H.R. 7097, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, H.R. 9811, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, Rice Hearing (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, Rice Hearing (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture, Sugar, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture, Wheat, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Appropriations (1 of 3), 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Appropriations (2 of 3), 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Appropriations (3 of 3), 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Armed Services (1 of 4), 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Armed Services (2 of 4), 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Armed Services (3 of 4), 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Armed Services (4 of 4), 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Armed Services, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Banking and Currency (1 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Banking and Currency (2 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Banking and Currency (3 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Banking and Currency (4 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Banking and Currency, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1959-1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Committees, General, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Committees, General, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Committees, General, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Committees, General, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Committees, Assignment Requests, 1964 November (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Committees, Assignment Requests, 1964 December (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Committees, Guide for the 88th Congress, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Education and Labor, General, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Education and Labor, General, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Education and Labor, General, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Education and Labor, General, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Education and Labor, Doubling Overtime Pay, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Education and Labor, Federal Aid to Education (1 of 3), 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Education and Labor, Federal Aid to Education (2 of 3), 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Education and Labor, Federal Aid to Education (3 of 3), 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Education and Labor, H.R. 10027, Common Situs Picketing Bill, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Education and Labor, H.R. 6041, Davis Beacon Act Amendment, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Education and Labor, H.R. 6060, Equal Pay Bill, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Education and Labor, Social Work Manpower Training Bill, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Education and Labor, H.R. 4955, Vocational Education Act, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Education and Labor, H.R. 9824, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Education and Labor, National Lunchroom and Milk Program, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Education and Labor, P.L. 89-10, Elementary and Secondary Education Act, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Education and Labor, Railroad Strike, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Education and Labor, Donation Program for Public Schools, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act, 1965 January-February (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act, 1965 March (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act, 1965 April (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (1 of 3), 1965 May (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (2 of 3), 1965 May (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (3 of 3), 1965 May (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (1 of 4), 1965 June (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (2 of 4), 1965 June (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (3 of 4), 1965 June (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (4 of 4), 1965 June (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (1 of 3), 1965 July (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (2 of 3), 1965 July (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act (3 of 3), 1965 July (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act, 1965 August (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Education and Labor, Section 14B of Taft-Hartley Act, 1965 September-1966 May (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Education and Labor, Wage and Hour Law, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Education and Labor, Wage and Hour Law, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Education and Labor, Wage and Hour Law, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Education and Labor, War on Poverty Bill, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Affairs, General, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs, General, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Affairs, Foreign Aid, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Affairs, Agency for International Development (1 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Affairs, Agency for International Development (2 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Affairs, Foreign Debts, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Affairs, Foreign Investors Tax, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Affairs, United Nations, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Government Operations, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Government Operations, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1963 January-April (Box 16, Folder 8)